we need to
add some more code to our name.rb
file that will print the name of the
user 10 times
let's run our name.rb file as it is
we're prompted for our name
i'll input bob and then the program
greets me
going back to our name.rb file we want
to
output the value referenced by the local
variable name
10 times and to output the name
we could simply invoke the put s method
and pass the name variable to it now
in this case we want to print the name
10 times
but we don't want to write the same line
of code
10 times in our file so we need to
figure out how to execute the code
written on line 5
10 times but only write it once
to do that we can use the integer times
method
we invoke the times method on an integer
in this case 10
and we pass it a block
and in our block we'll put the code that
we want to execute
when this code runs ruby will iterate
through the block
10 times this means that the code on
line 8
where we print the user's name will be
executed 10 times
even though we've only written it once
so let's run our code to see
this
i'll input bob as the user's name
the program greets us and then outputs
bob 10 times
and that's the behavior we were
expecting